My name is Chief Ikenna Victor Egbuna.
I am a native of Onicha (Nigeria).
I am a lawyer. I'm also a chartered insurer and chartered accountant.
I have come to give all glory to the Almighty for lifting me from the valley to the mountaintop.
My problem started in 1986 when I came back from my national youth service.
I happened to come from a family of idol worshippers.
I am a descendant of red cap chiefs on both sides.
I was only 9 years old when my father died.
Because of the challenges in the family, I became very close to my mother.
In fact, I was usually referred to as her handbag.
But when I came back from the youth service,
one day, one of my uncles came and told my mother that they went to consult an idol
to find out why members of my family die at a very young age.
After the consultation, as they were leaving, the woman was calling them,
"Come, come! Ikenna, Ikenna!"
And they asked, "Why?"
She said, "Look, there is a young man in your family who is a lawyer.
His name is Ikenna, and he is going to die!"
So, my mother started panicking and asked, "What do we do?"
He said, "The priestess said they should bring me".
So, they took me to the lady with my elder sister, she performed her concoctions,
used a razor blade to give me marks and inserted those things on my body.
From that day, my mother hated me with passion and everything I did was not acceptable to her.
In my professional background - I started my career as a lawyer -
in fact, within six months, my principal asked me to leave his office.
I tried to get another place to work - I did not.
At a point, because I was proficient in mathematics, I started looking for what else to do.
I started studying insurance.
It took me seven years to qualify as an associate of the Chartered Insurance Institute, London.
I became a chartered insurer.
I started looking for jobs. I would apply and be shortlisted.
The day the application would be unsealed, it would be discovered that I did not even sign it.
I looked for other jobs - assistant general manager at Ajaokuta Steel,
secretary NJSC, chief registrar at court - there must be one problem along the line.
But one thing that is significant, is that at every of such application,
I would have a dream - a strange woman would come and sleep with me.
After that, everything about that would go.
That continued until I heard about The SCOAN, and I came to meet with the man of God.
When I met him one-on-one, he gave me this Morning Water and this booklet
titled 'What The Future Holds'. He signed his signature on it and gave it to me.
From that day, my destiny started the journey of restoration.
Before, I would go to court, do a case very well but would not be able to collect money.
In some cases, I did not even collect a dime.
Later, with the visit to The SCOAN, I no longer witnessed any strange person coming to sleep with me.
I dropped the certificates of insurance and accounting
and went back to my original profession - the legal profession.
One night, after praying with the man of God on the screen
and administering the Morning Water, I saw him in the dream.
I discovered myself in my first office.
I discovered I was lying helplessly in the office
and the protector was locked with about three keys.
I was locked up inside that office.
And the man of God came.
When I saw him, I jumped up, "Man of God! Man of God!"
He just opened the keys and asked me to come out.
And I came out.
From that day, my destiny started a very fsst recovery journey.
And today, I am a Senior Advocate of Nigeria.
That is the highest professional accomplishment in the legal profession.
I was sworn in on the 18th of September, 2017.
In the list, which is on this board, I am Number 7,
out of the 30 people that were made senior advocates.
Over 500 people applied, 169 were shortlisted and only 30 were awarded the rank.
And I am Number 7 among them.
The picture you see here is myself in my full regalia as a Senior Advocate of Nigeria.
This one is the one we took at the Supreme Court on the Swearing-In Day with my dear wife.
This one too is also a photograph we took on that day
with my brother-in-the-Lord Oche Nabi Esquire, Senior Advocate of Nigeria.
On the board here - I attended the University of Ife where I graduated in 1984.
This is my graduation certificate.
I was called to the bar in 1985. This is my certificate.
I became an associate of the Chartered Insurance Institute, London.
This is my qualification, my certificate.
Now, because the Insurance Institute, London, is the first all over the world,
if you are a member of that institute, you can get a job anywhere.
When I got frustrated in Nigeria, I applied to England, to formally elect me as an associate.
And in 2004, they did. This is the certificate.
I read my accountancy at the University of Ife. This is my certificate.
I became a member of the Association of National Accountants in 2001.
So, sir, with all of these certificates and qualifications,
you mean, you were still experiencing such severe stagnation
until you encountered Jesus Christ here at The SCOAN.
Yes. The only thing that worked in my life was reading 24 hours in a day and passing exams.
But I never got any job.
It was only when I came to The SCOAN, where I was given the Morning Water
and the man of God released me from the 'spiritual sale' I didn't know I was in
that my destiny started shining again.
I started getting big briefs again and now, I am a Senior Advocate of Nigeria.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Tell us - after you encountered Jesus here, what changes have you experienced in that area,
in terms of your relationship with your family.
My relationship with my mother changed.
On day, she called me on the phone and asked, "Where are you?"
I told her. She said, "I want to see you".
When I went to see her, she said, "Ikenna, I don't know what happened between us".
It is as clear as daylight that it was that demonic influence of that...
I don't know whether it was the initiation they did to me that caused the whole thing.
Today, our relationship is restored. I am back as her handbag.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sir, you said, before, you were plagued with such terrible nightmares,
sleeping with women at the point of breakthrough in your dreams.
Just tell us - after you came here, what changed in that area?
As soon as I came here, I stopped having such experience.
In fact, the last experience I had - somebody came and I said, "I don't know who you are!"
She started trying to convince me and I saw myself beating her,
something I have never done in my life. I gave her serious blows and she had to run away.
And that was the last time I experienced that in my life.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
When I compiled my applications - because for the application as Senior Advocate,
you compile judgements you have obtained that are landmark judgements.
In fact, they are contained in about four big 'Ghana-must-go' (plastic bags).
What I did was to place the man of God's signature on it.
Every two days I would change it to the other one.
It was after about 8 days that I decided to go and submit the application.
And in my mind I was convinced that my application had the signature of the Almighty.
And indeed, it was successful. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Children of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
In fact, as you can see, I am so happy!
I don't know how to thank the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
After 31 years of stagnation in practice,
we had an encounter with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Our sorrow turned to joy and testimonies.
And my husband has said it all.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
My word of advice goes like this:
Prophet T.B. Joshua is God's ambassador extraordinary and plenipotentiary.
I say so on the following grounds:
One, The SCOAN is the biggest healing and therapeutic centre all over the world.
Two, Prophet T.B. Joshua is God's biggest micro and macro economist
who predicts the economy of the whole world with precision, without statistics.
Three, Prophet T.B. Joshua is God's inspector general of the whole world.
He predicts security challenges - be it in Syria, North Korea, United States - and proffers solutions.
Number Four, The SCOAN and Prophet T.B. Joshua have created a platform
for hundreds of thousands of people to see God.
I am talking about the Emmanuel TV Partners who go about the whole world doing good.
Number Five, Prophet T.B. Joshua is a man overly endowed with Christian urbanity.
I am talking about his reconcilitation ministry, his being father to the fatherless,
and in fact, hope to the hopeless.
Number Six, Prophet T.B. Joshua is one of the few positive images of this country.
If you go outside Nigeria, the only thing you hear about Nigerians are negative things.
But it is only because of Prophet T.B. Joshua that many countries have established
and others are seeking to establish diplomatic relations with Nigeria.
Finally, my advice is that anybody - be him a Nigerian or a foreigner -
who has not visited The SCOAN is cheating himself. Thank you.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!